Guide to the Anthony Barboza papers, ca. 1970-1999.
Barboza, Anthony papers
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Anthony Barboza papers, ca. 1970-1999.
6839
Anthony Barboza 1944-
6 cubic feet.
Photographs
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Photographs and ephemera relating to jazz musicians, African-American artists, dancers, writers, and the New York Scene, 1970s-1990s.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
1,000 black-and-white and color photographs of prominent jazz musicians, African-American artists, dancers, writers, and the New York Scene, 1970s-1990s; 200 tech sheets from studio portrait shoots; 27 transcripts of interviews with jazz musicians (various drafts); 24 original recordings of interviews on audio tapes; 1 original tape of Henry Threadgill's Very Very Circus "Makin a Move"; 56 pieces of jazz and photograph ephemera, 1980s and 1990s including alternative museum announcements, jazz concerts, party invitations, promotional materials from artists, show announcements, postcards of artwork; 6 buttons; 2 posters from photo exhibitions, 1990s; "Black Borders" (book).
Additional 1,000 photographs, including images of jazz musicians, fashion photographs, celebrity photographs, and some pictures of urban life; collection of memorabilia from the 1993 Blue Note Jazz festival; notes and photographs from Barboza's "Portrait on the Roof" shoot; posters, programs, invitations, jazz magazines and journals; ephemera from Barboza's life and career including calendars, books, flyers, catalogs, invitations, and technical documents (tear sheets and tech sheets) from various shoots; reproductions, resumes, and announcements relating to the "Kamoinge" group of African American photographers; cassette tapes and video tapes.
Jazz musicians of the 80s: poster, with group photograph of 1980s jazz musicians, all identified, signed by the photographer. Photographer: Anthony Barboza; Designer: Clemente Ettrick.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Barboza, Anthony, 1944-; Ettrick, Clemente.; Threadgill, Henry.
Subjects:
African American photographers.; African American artists -- United States; Jazz musicians -- United States
Form and Genre Terms:
Photographs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
All the photographs are individually numbered and should be kept in order in the boxes.
Photograph boxes by size:
Small - 5" x 7" Box 8
Medium - 8" x 10" Boxes: 4, 15, 22
Large - 11" x 14" Boxes: 1-3, 9, 11, 12, 19-21, 26, 27
Extra Large - 14" x 17", 16" x 20" Boxes: 5, 10, 13, 14, 17, 18, 23-25
Oversize - 20" x 24" Boxes: 6, 7, 16
SERIES LIST
Series I. Photographs
Boxes 1-26
Jazz Musicians
Other Music Related
Actors, Artists and Celebrities
Fashion
People and Places
Miscellaneous
Series II. Posters
Mapcase
Series II. Documents
Boxes 27, 32-33
Series II. Audio Recordings
Boxes 28-31
CONTAINER LIST
- Photographs
  - Jazz Musicians
    - Michael Richards Abrams, 1989; 330-331 (Box 4)
    - A.I.R., 1983; 332 (Box 4)
      With Steve McCall, Fred Hopkins, Henry Threadgill
    - Kamal Abdul Alim, November 1983; 1-2 (Box 1)
    - Art Ensemble of Chicago, December 1979 - August 1983; 3-18 (Box 1)
      Lester Bowie, Joseph Jarman, Don Moye, Malachi Favors, Roscoe Mitchell
    - Art Ensemble of Chicago, 1981 - 1983; 333-340 (Box 4)
      With Lester Bowie, Joseph Jarman, Malachi Favors, Roscoe Mitchell and Don Moye
    - Art Ensemble of Chicago, 1979, 1983; 575-581 (Box 6)
      At Public Theatre, Bottom Line
    - Art Ensemble of Chicago, 1983; 681 (Box 8)
      At the Bottom Line
    - Bobby Battle, June 1988; 19 (Box 1)
    - Bobby Battle, 1984; 682-686 (Box 8)
      At Village Vanguard
    - John Betsch, May 1984; 687-690 (Box 8)
      At Sweet Basil
    - Big Nick Nicholas, 1980; 20-23 (Box 1)
    - Walter Bishop Jr., 1984; 691-692 (Box 8)
      At Lush Life
    - Alfonzo Blackwell, May 2001; 24-25 (Box 1)
    - Terence Blanchard, April 1989; 582 (Box 6)
    - Blue Note Festival, February 1985; 341-342 (Box 4)
    - Hamiet Bluiett, 1979-1989; 26-45 (Box 1)
      With sextet, Olu Dara, Walter Booker Jr. At Lush Life, Carlos I, Sweet Basil, in the studio.
    - Hamiet Bluiett, 1980; 343-345 (Box 4)
      With Michael Carver, World Sax Quarter. At Symphony Space, Tracks
    - Hamiet Bluiett, 1977-1982; 529-534 (Box 5)
      Multiple underexposed or damaged photos.
    - Hamiet Bluiett, 1980 - 1988; 583-594 (Box 6)
      With Olu Dara, Fred Hopkins, his sextet. At Trax, Sweet Basil, Carlos I,
    - Arthur Blythe, 1981, 1988; 46-50 (Box 1)
      At Village Vanguard, 7th Ave South
    - Arthur Blythe, 1980 - 1989; 283-298 (Box 3)
      With Cecil Taylor, Arthur Blythe, Fred Hopkins.
      At Tin Palace, Fat Tuesday's, Cecil Taylor's Loft, Sweet Basil, The Kitchen,
    - Arthur Blythe, 1980 - 1988; 346-350 (Box 4)
      With Fred Hopkins, Philip Wilson. At Sweet Basil, Village Vanguard, 7th Ave South
    - Arthur Blythe, 1983; 535 (Box 5)
    - Arthur Blythe, January 1981; 595 (Box 6)
      At 7th Ave South
    - Walter Booker Jr., May 1984; 51-52 (Box 1)
    - Walter Booker Jr., May 1984; 536-537 (Box 5)
    - Walter Booker Jr., May 1984; 596 (Box 6)
      With John Hicks Band. At Lush Life
    - Lester Bowie, 1984-1989; 53-63 (Box 1)
      With Cecil McBee, The Leaders. At Sweet Basil, Catalina Bar
    - Lester Bowie, 1983 - 1988; 351-363 (Box 4)
      With Art Ensemble of Chicago, Brass Fantasy. At Bottom Line, Sweet Basil,
    - Lester Bowie, 1984 -; 597-600 (Box 6)
      With The Leaders. At Sweet Basil, Catalina Bar
    - Bradley's NYC, July 1996; 364-365 (Box 4)
      Shot for New Yorker Magazine
    - Bradley's NYC, July 1996; 693-696 (Box 8)
    - Brass Fantasy, 1984, 1989; 64-68 (Box 1)
      Lester Bowie with Philip Wilson, Vincent Chancey, Bob Stewart, Craig Harris, Malachi Thompson, Steve Turre, Bruce Purse. At Sweet Basil.
    - Brass Fantasy, 1984-1989; 366-373 (Box 4)
      At Sweet Basil, Studio
    - Brass Fantasy, October 1989; 601-605 (Box 6)
    - Kenny Burrell, February 1985; 374-375 (Box 4)
      At Blue Note Festival
    - Kenny Burrell, 1985; 697-698 (Box 8)
      With Lou Donaldson. At Blue Note rehearsal
    - Don Byron, August 1993; 69-79 (Box 1)
      At Knitting Factory. Shot for New York Times Sunday Magazine
    - Cameo, March 1985; 80-83 (Box 1)
      With Larry Blackmon, Tomi Jenkins, Nathan Leftenant
    - Carlos I, 1988; 84-85 (Box 1)
    - Baikida Carrol, May 1984; 699 (Box 8)
    - Diahann Carroll, 1971; 86-87 (Box 1)
      Shot for Essence Magazine
    - Betty Carter, 1977, 1986; 88-91 (Box 1)
    - Betty Carter, 1976, 1996; 376-378 (Box 4)
    - Betty Carter, 1976; 538-539 (Box 5)
    - Betty Carter, 1977, 1990; 606-607 (Box 6)
      With quartet. At Bottom Line
    - Ron Carter, February 1985; 379-381 (Box 4)
    - Michael Carvin, October 1989; 540-541 (Box 5)
      With Andrew Cyrille. At Knitting Factory
    - Michael Carvin, October 1989; 608 (Box 6)
      With Andrew Cyrille. At the Knitting Factory
    - Vincent Chancey, 1984 - 1985; 92-94 (Box 1)
    - Vincent Chancey, May 1984; 700-701 (Box 8)
    - Don Cherry, April 1989; 702-703 (Box 8)
      At Continental Divide
    - Ornette Coleman, 1977, 1997; 95-99 (Box 1)
      1997 shot for New Yorker Magazine
    - Ornette Coleman, June 1997; 704-705 (Box 8)
      At 125th St Loft. Shot for New Yorker Magazine
    - Steve Coleman, May 1984; 706-707 (Box 8)
    - Norman Connors, 1970s; 100 (Box 1)
    - Cozy Cole, September 1984; 101 (Box 1)
      At Village Gate
    - Hank Crawford, 1978; 102-103 (Box 1)
    - Hank Crawford, 1978; 542 (Box 5)
    - Olu Dara, 1980 - 1987; 223-229 (Box 2)
      With Henry Threadgill Sextet, Warren Smith, Hamiet Bluiett Sextet. At Tin Palace, Sweet Basil, Village Gate.
    - Olu Dara's Okra Orchestra, 1980; 230-232 (Box 2)
    - Olu Dara, 1981-1991; 382-386 (Box 4)
      With Henry Threadgill Sextet, Olu Dara's son. At Village Gate, 450 West 31st Loft. Shot for New York Times Sunday Magazine
    - Olu Dara, 1980-1983; 609-613 (Box 6)
      With his Okra Orchestra, Henry Threadgill Sextet, Hamiet Bluiett Sextet.
      At 450 W 31st St. Loft, Brooklyn loft, Sweet Basil
    - Miles Davis, 1971, 1984; 104-112 (Box 1)
      Shots for Essence Magazine, for Columbia Records
    - Miles Davis, 1971-1985; 387-395 (Box 4)
      Shot for New York Times Sunday Magazine, Essence Magazine, album shoot
    - Miles Davis, 1971, 1985; 543-550 (Box 5)
      At home. Shot for Essence Magazine
    - Miles Davis, 1985; 614-616 (Box 6)
      Shot for New York Times Sunday Magazine, for album cover
    - Miles Davis, 1985; 708 (Box 8)
      Shot for New York Times Sunday Magazine
    - Walter Davis, February 1985; 396-397 (Box 4)
    - Jack DeJohnette, February 1985; 398-399 (Box 4)
    - Lou Donaldson, February 1985; 400-401 (Box 4)
    - Lou Donaldson, 1985; 709-710 (Box 8)
      With Kenny Burrell. At Blue Note rehearsal
    - Ray Drummond, May 1985; 113 (Box 1)
    - Ray Drummond, 1989; 617 (Box 6)
    - Art Farmer, 1978; 711 (Box 8)
    - Sonny Fortune, 1979; 114-115 (Box 2)
    - Frank Foster, 1997; 116 (Box 2)
      With swing and dance band
    - Chico Freeman, 1979-1991; 117-126 (Box 2)
      With Steve McCall, The Leaders. At Fat Tuesday's, Catalina Club. Shot for New York Times Sunday Magazine
    - Chico Freeman, 1979, 1988, 1996; 402-405 (Box 4)
      With Steve McCall, Cecil McBee, Jay Hoggard, The Leaders.
      At Fat Tuesday's, Catalina Club, Visions
    - Chico Freeman, 1979, 1988; 618-621 (Box 6)
      With quartet: Cecil McBee, Jay Hoggard, Victor, and other; The Leaders. At Fat Tuesday's, Catalina Bar
    - Chico Freeman, May 1996; 712 (Box 8)
      At Visions
    - Curtis Fuller, February 1985; 406 (Box 4)
    - Curtis Fuller, 1985; 713 (Box 8)
      At Blue Note rehearsal
    - Dizzy Gillespie, September 1988; 127 (Box 2)
      At Blue Note
    - Dizzy Gillespie, September 1988; 407-410 (Box 4)
    - Dizzy Gillespie, July 1976; 622 (Box 6)
      At the Newport Jazz Fesitval
    - Max Gordon, June 1988; 411 (Box 4)
      Owner of the Village Vanguard
    - Johnny Griffin, July 1976; 128 (Box 2)
      At the Newport Jazz Festival
    - Johnny Griffin, February 1985; 412-413 (Box 4)
    - Chico Hamilton, 1971; 129 (Box 2)
      With wife and daughter. Shot for Essence Magazine
    - Chico Hamilton, 1971; 414-417 (Box 4)
    - Pat Hammond, 1975; 418 (Box 4)
    - Pat Hammond, 1975; 551 (Box 5)
    - Lionel Hampton, 1987; 130-131 (Box 2)
    - Lionel Hampton, 1987; 419 (Box 4)
    - Lionel Hampton, 1984; 623 (Box 6)
    - Herbie Hancock, February 1985; 420-421 (Box 4)
    - Herbie Hancock, 1985; 714 (Box 8)
    - D. Antoinette Handy, 1993; 132-133 (Box 2)
      Shot for Aetna Calendar
    - Katherine Lewis Handy, 1974; 134-135 (Box 2)
      Daughter of W.C. Handy
    - Philip Harper, 1989; 136 (Box 2)
    - Philip Harper, 1989; 552 (Box 5)
    - Philip and Winard Harper, 1989; 624 (Box 6)
    - Winard Harper, 1989; 137 (Box 2)
    - Winard Harper, 1989; 553 (Box 5)
    - Craig Harris, 1980, 1984, 1989; 138-144 (Box 2)
      With his band, Phillip Wilson. At Sweet Basil, Tin Palace
    - Craig Harris, 1984 - 1987; 424-429 (Box 4)
      With his band. At Sweet Basil
    - Craig Harris, 1980, 1984; 554-555 (Box 5)
      At Tin Palace
    - Craig Harris, 1981 - 1989; 625-628 (Box 6)
      With Henry Threadgill Sextet. At 450 W 31st St. Loft, Sweet Basil
    - Craig Harris, May 1984; 715-718 (Box 8)
    - Donald Harrison, April 1989; 145 (Box 2)
    - Julius Hemphill, 1977 - 1980; 146-150 (Box 2)
      At TR3, Hurrah, Trax
    - Joe Henderson, February 1985; 422-423 (Box 4)
    - John Hicks, 1981 - 1988; 151-160 (Box 2)
      With The Leaders. At 7th Ave South, Lush Life, Catalina Bar, in studio.
    - John Hicks, May 1984; 629 (Box 6)
      With Hamiet Bluiett, Walter Booker Jr. At Lush Life
    - John Hicks, 1984, 1991; 719-728 (Box 8)
      With band; Ray Drummond, Brandford Marsalis. At Sweet Basil
    - Jay Hoggard, 1980; 161 (Box 2)
    - Fred Hopkins, 1980 - 1988; 162-167 (Box 2)
      With Hamiet Bluiett sextet. At Cecil Taylor's Loft, Sweet Basil
    - Fred Hopkins, 1980 - 1989; 283-298 (Box 3)
    - Fred Hopkins, 1980 - 1981; 556-557 (Box 5)
      With John Hicks. At 7th Ave South
    - Fred Hopkins, 1980, 1984; 630-632 (Box 6)
      At Sweet Basil, Cecil Taylor's loft
    - Freddie Hubbard, 1982; 168 (Box 2)
    - Freddie Hubbard, February 1985; 430-432 (Box 4)
    - Freddie Hubbard, 1985; 633-635 (Box 6)
      At rehearsal for Blue Note concert
    - Freddie Hubbard, 1985; 729-733 (Box 8)
      With Johnny Griffin, Curtis Fuller. At Blue Note rehearsal
    - Bobby Hutcherson, February 1985; 433-434 (Box 4)
    - Phyllis Hyman, May 1978; 169 (Box 2)
    - Joseph Jarman, 1985; 734-735 (Box 8)
      With Henry Threadgill
    - Jazz Musician Signatures, 1951 (Map-case Z-19, Folder 1)
    - Leroy Jenkins, 1978; 170-174 (Box 2)
    - Leroy Jenkins, 1978; 558 (Box 5)
    - Robert Jordan, 1976; 435 (Box 4)
    - Stanley Jordan, February 1985; 436-438 (Box 4)
    - Frank Lacey, 1988; 636 (Box 7)
      With Hamiet Bluiett Sextet. At Carlos I
    - Steve Lacey, 1988; 175-177 (Box 2)
      At Carlos I
    - Oliver Lake, 1977, 1983; 178-181 (Box 2)
      With his band
    - Oliver Lake, 1980, 1985; 439-441 (Box 4)
      With World Sax Quartet, Michael Gregory Jackson, Pheeroan akLaff. At Tracks
    - Oliver Lake, 1977; 559 (Box 5)
    - Oliver Lake, 1980; 637-642 (Box 7)
      With World Sax Quartet. At Trax, Hurrah,
    - The Leaders, 1988, 1991; 182-184 (Box 2)
      With Arthur Blythe, Lester Bowie, Chico Freeman. At Catalina Bar, Sweet Basil
    - The Leaders, 1988, 1991; 442-444 (Box 4)
      With Lester Bowie, Chico Freeman, Arthur Blythe. At Catalina Bar, Sweet Basil
    - Kirk Lightsey, 1988; 185 (Box 2)
    - Kirk Lightsey, December 1988; 643 (Box 7)
      With The Leaders. At Catalina Bar
    - Abbey Lincoln, 1980; 186-188 (Box 2)
      At Symphony Space
    - Abbey Lincoln, June 1980; 644-645 (Box 7)
    - Arthur Lion, February 1985; 445 (Box 4)
      With Bruce Lundvall. At Blue Note Festival
    - Charles Lloyd, February 1985; 446-447 (Box 4)
    - Jon Lucian, 1975-1976; 189-190 (Box 2)
    - Jimmy Lyons, November 1984; 191 (Box 2)
      Backstage at Cecil Taylor Live
    - Jimmy Lyons, November 1984; 448 (Box 4)
      At Cecil Taylor Live
    - Jimmy Lyons, November 1984; 646 (Box 7)
    - Branford Marsalis, 1984, 1990; 192-194 (Box 2)
      With John Hicks Band. At Lush Life. Shot for New York Times Sunday Magazine
    - Brandford Marsalis, 1990; 647 (Box 7)
    - Wynton Marsalis, May 2000; 449-452 (Box 4)
    - Hugh Masekela, 1980; 453 (Box 4)
      With Miriam Makeba
    - Hugh Masekela, 1980; 560 (Box 5)
    - Cecil McBee, May 1979; 195 (Box 2)
      At Fat Tuesday's
    - Cecil McBee, February 1985; 454-455 (Box 4)
    - Cecil McBee, May 1979; 648 (Box 7)
    - Christian McBride, 1992; 456 (Box 4)
      With Antonio Hart, Stephen Scott, Roy Hargrove, Cassandra Wilson, Winard Harper
    - Steve McCall, 1984; 196 (Box 2)
    - Steve McCall, 1980; 561 (Box 5)
    - Jackie McClean, February 1985; 457-460 (Box 4)
    - Butch Morris, November 1984; 197-198 (Box 2)
      Shot for Village Voice
    - Butch Morris, 1985; 649 (Box 7)
      At Greene St. Bar
    - Butch Morris, 1984-1985; 736-739 (Box 8)
      With David Murray band; Vincent Chancey, Craig Harris. At Sweet Basil, The Kitchen
    - Don Moye, December 1988; 650 (Box 7)
    - Mtume, 1975; 199-204 (Box 2)
    - Mtume, 1975; 821 (Box 9)
    - The Muffett Family, April 1980; 461 (Box 4)
    - Idris Muhammad, 1978; 205 (Box 2)
    - Idris Muhammad, 1978; 462 (Box 4)
    - Idris Muhammad, 1978; 562 (Box 5)
    - Idris Muhammad, 1984; 652 (Box 7)
    - David Murray, 1976 - 1984; 206-215 (Box 2)
      With Ming Smith, World Sax Quartet. At Trax, TR3, Sweet Basil.
    - David Murray, 1980-1984; 463-468 (Box 4)
      With World Sax Quartet. At Sweet Basil, Hurrah, Tracks
    - David Murray, 1975, 1980; 563-564 (Box 5)
      With World Sax Quartet
    - David Murray, 1980, 1984; 653-656 (Box 7)
      With World Sax Quartet. At Trax, Sweet Basil
    - David Murray, 1984; 740-741 (Box 8)
    - Diedre Murray, 1984; 657 (Box 7)
    - Musamba, 1984; 469 (Box 4)
    - Musumba, 1984; 651 (Box 7)
    - Phineas Newborn, May 1984; 216 (Box 2)
    - Phineas Newborn, May 1984; 742-744 (Box 8)
    - Newport Jazz Festival, July 1976; 217-221 (Box 2)
    - James Newton, February 1985; 470-471 (Box 4)
    - Mike Nock, 1978; 222 (Box 2)
    - Mike Nock, 1978; 745 (Box 8)
    - Greg Osby, May 1985; 233 (Box 2)
    - Freda Payne, 1971; 234 (Box 3)
    - Michael Petrucciani, February 1985; 472-473 (Box 4)
    - Joshua Redman, 1995; 474 (Box 4)
    - Sam Rivers, 1978; 235-236 (Box 3)
    - Max Roach, June 1970; 237 (Box 3)
    - Max Roach, 1980; 475-477 (Box 4)
    - Max Roach, 1988; 746 (Box 8)
    - Sonny Rollins, June 1974; 238-244 (Box 3)
    - Pharoah Sanders, June 1974, 1978; 245-249 (Box 3)
    - Pharaoh Sanders, 1978; 565-566 (Box 5)
    - 7th Avenue South, January 1981; 250 (Box 3)
    - 7th Ave South, January 22, 1981; 478 (Box 4)
    - Woody Shaw, 1984; 251-253 (Box 3)
    - Woody Shaw, 1981, 1985; 479-482 (Box 4)
      At Village Vanguard, Blue Note Festival
    - Woody Shaw, 1985; 747 (Box 8)
      At Blue Note Rehearsal
    - Smalls Jazz Club, July 1996; 254 (Box 3)
    - Small's Jazz Club, July 29, 1996; 483-485 (Box 4)
    - Small's Jazz Club, July 1996; 748-753 (Box 8)
    - Bessie Smith, 1920s; 486 (Box 4)
      From the collection of Anthony Barboza
    - Jimmy Smith, February 1985; 487-488 (Box 4)
    - Jimmy Smith, 1985; 754-756 (Box 8)
    - Spooner, 1980; 255 (Box 3)
    - Sun Ra's Arkestra, 1985, 1987; 256-264 (Box 3)
      At Sweet Basil, Knitting Factory
    - Sun Ra's Arkestra, 1985, 1987; 489-493 (Box 4)
    - Sun Ra, 1987; 567 (Box 5)
      Knitting Factory
    - Sun Ra's Arkestra, 1985, 1987; 658-663 (Box 7)
    - Sun Ra, 1987-1988; 757-761 (Box 8)
      With his Arkestra. At Knitting Factory, Sweet Basil
    - Sweet Basil, 1980-1984; 494-501 (Box 4)
    - Sweet Basil, 1985; 665 (Box 7)
    - Sweet Basil, May 1984; 762 (Box 8)
    - Symphony Space, June 1980; 664 (Box 7)
    - Grady Tate, February 1985; 502 (Box 4)
    - Cecil Taylor, 1980-1989; 265-278 (Box 3)
      At his loft, Fat Tuesday's, Irving Plaza
    - Cecil Taylor, 1980 - 1985; 503-510 (Box 4)
      At Fat Tuesday's, in his loft, at Blue Note Festival
    - Cecil Taylor, 1980; 279-282 (Box 3)
      Rehearsal at Cecil Taylor's Loft with Cecil Taylor, Jim Lyons, Henry Threadgill
    - Cecil Taylor, 1980 - 1989; 283-298 (Box 3)
    - Cecil Taylor, 1980; 568 (Box 5)
    - Cecil Taylor, 1980, 1989; 666-668 (Box 7)
      At Fat Tuesday's, his loft, Sweet Basil
    - Cecil Taylor, 1989; 763-764 (Box 8)
    - Henry Threadgill, 1980s; 511-512 (Box 4)
      With his sextet, Philip Wilson. At Sweet Basil
    - Henry Threadgill, 1980; 569 (Box 5)
    - Henry Threadgill, 1980-1988; 669-673 (Box 7)
      With his sextet, Fred Hopkins, Olu Dara, Joseph Jarman. At Tin Palace, Alternative Center, Village Vanguard
    - Henry Threadgill, 1980-1985; 765-780 (Box 8)
      With sextet; Philip Wilson, Craig Harris, Fred Hopkins, Olu Dara, Joseph Jarman. At Tin Palace, 450 W 31st St Loft, Sweet Basik
    - Henry Threadgill, 1980, 1983; 1947-1948 (Map-case Z-19, Folder 1)
    - Stanley Turrentine, 1985; 299 (Box 3)
    - Stanley Turrentine, February 1985; 513-514 (Box 4)
    - Village Gate, 1987; 300-308 (Box 3)
    - Village Gate, 1984; 674 (Box 7)
    - Village Vanguard, 1983, 1988; 309-314 (Box 3)
      With Arthur Blythe
    - Village Vanguard, June 1974; 570-571 (Box 5)
    - Village Vanguard, June 1988; 675 (Box 7)
    - Bernie Wallace, February 1985; 515 (Box 4)
    - Grover Washington, Jr., February 1985; 516-519 (Box 4)
      With Alfred Lion. At Blue Note Festival
    - Booker T. Williams, 1987; 315 (Box 3)
      At S.O.B.'s
    - Booker T. Williams, 1987; 676-677b (Box 7)
      With Henry Threadgill. At S.O.B's
    - Tony Williams, February 1985; 520-521 (Box 4)
    - Cassandra Wilson, 1988; 316-317 (Box 3)
    - Cassandra Wilson, 1988; 522 (Box 4)
    - Philip Wilson, June 1980; 318 (Box 3)
    - Reggie Workman, 1983; 319 (Box 3)
    - Reggie Workman, 1985, 1988; 523-525 (Box 4)
      At Blue Note Festival, Village Vanguard
    - Reggie Workman, 1983; 781 (Box 8)
    - World Sax Quartet, 1977-1980; 320-327 (Box 3)
      With David Murray, Julius Hemphill, Hamiet Bluiett, Oliver Lake. At The 80's, Trax, Hurrah
    - World Sax Quartet, April 1980; 526-528 (Box 4)
      At the 80s club, Trax
    - World Sax Quartet, 1977 - 1980; 572-574 (Box 5)
      At the 80s Club
    - World Sax Quartet, 1980; 678-679 (Box 7)
      At the 80s, TR3
    - World Saxophone Quarter, 1980; 1950 (Map-case Z-19, Folder 1)
    - Unlabeled Jazz Musicians, October 3, 1983; 328 (Box 3)
      On 108 East 16th Street Rooftop
    - Unlabeled Jazz Musician, 329 (Box 3)
    - Unlabeled Saxophonist, 680 (Box 7)
  - Other Music Related
    - Erykah Badu, 2000; 782-784 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Mary J. Blige, June 1999; 785-788 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Bow Wow, 2002; 805 (Box 9)
    - Bow Wow, 2002; 830-831 (Box 10)
    - Sonya Cohen, June 1997; 789-790 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      With Dick Connette
    - Dick Connette, June 1997; 791 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Frankie Crocker, 1970, 1976; 806-808 (Box 9)
    - Roberta Flack, 1971; 809-813 (Box 9)
    - Roberta Flack, 1971; 832-834a (Box 10)
    - Grandmaster Flash, October 1984; 814-816 (Box 9)
    - Vivian Green, 2003; 835 (Box 10)
    - Vivian Green, 2003; 1921 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Lauryn Hill, 1998; 817 (Box 9)
    - Freddie Jackson, 2003; 836 (Box 10)
    - Michael Jackson, 1977; 792 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Michael Jackson, 1977; 837 (Box 10)
    - Millie Jackson, 1979; 818 (Box 9)
    - Jay-Z, January 2000; 793-794 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Jay-Z, January 2000; 819 (Box 9)
      Shot for USA Weekend
    - Jay-Z, January 2000; 838-839 (Box 10)
    - Robert Jordan, 1976; 840-840a (Box 10)
    - Alicia Keys, 2001; 795 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      For Essence Magazine
    - B.B. King, 1971; 803-804 (Box 9)
      And his guitar with models. Shot for Essence Magazine.
    - B.B. King, 1971; 828-829 (Box 10)
    - Talib Kweli, April 2001; 796 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Living Colour, 1983; 841 (Box 10)
      With Corey Glover, Muzz Skillings, Vernon Reid, Will Calhoun
    - Miriam Makeba, 1980; 842 (Box 10)
    - Marian Makeba, 1980; 1922 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Kurt Mazur, 1991; 797 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Kurt Mazur, 1991; 820 (Box 9)
    - Mos Def, 1999; 798 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Mos Def, 1999-2000; 843-844 (Box 10)
      Shot for BlackBook Magazine
    - Next, 1998; 822 (Box 9)
    - Salt-N-Pepa, July 1997; 799-800 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Salt-N-Pepa, July 1997; 823 (Box 9)
    - Ravi Shankar, 1988; 824 (Box 9)
      Shot for Life Magazine
    - Ravi Shankar, 1988; 845 (Box 10)
    - Russell Simmons, 1990s; 825 (Box 9)
      With musicians
    - Sylvester, 1980; 846-846a (Box 10)
    - Caetano Veloso, April 2001; 826 (Box 9)
    - Bill Withers, 1971; 801 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Bill Withers, 1971; 827 (Box 9)
    - Unlabeled Musicians, 1991; 802 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Actors, Artists and Celebrities
    - Walter Abish, April 1991; 1046-1047 (Box 13)
      Author
    - Debbie Allen, 1979; 847-848 (Box 11)
      Dancer
    - Debbie Allen, 1979; 1048-1050 (Box 13)
    - Debbie Allen, 1979; 1164-1165 (Box 15)
    - Melody Anderson, 1979; 849-850 (Box 11)
      Actress
    - Toyce Anderson, 1980; 851 (Box 11)
      Collagist
    - Toyce Anderson, 1980; 1051 (Box 13)
      Artist, costume designer
    - Benny Andrews, 1975; 1052 (Box 13)
      Artist
    - Benny Andrews, June 1975; 1166-1168 (Box 15)
      Artist. Shot for Black Enterprise Magazine
    - Benny Andrews, 1975; 1923 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Steve B, 1975; 1053 (Box 13)
      Writer
    - James Baldwin, 1975; 1054 (Box 13)